University of Arizona Office of the President records, 1937-1947
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Events: Dedication to the Douglas Memorial Building for Mines and Metallurgy. May 27, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Events: Harry Elmer Barnes Lectures. April 1941 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Events: 2nd Inter-American Conference on Agriculture, Mexico City. Includes correspondence, President Atkinson's address, photo and miscellaneous publications. July 6, 1942 - July 16, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Events: 2nd Inter-American Conference on Agriculture, Mexico City. Includes correspondence, President Atkinson's address, photo and miscellaneous publications. July 6, 1942 - July 16, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Events: 2nd Inter-American Conference on Agriculture, Mexico City. Includes correspondence, President Atkinson's address, photo and miscellaneous publications. July 6, 1942 - July 16, 1942 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Events: Assembly and Honorary Degree for Viscount Halifax, British Ambassordor. May 10, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Events: Chirstmas Programs 1937-1947 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous: Memoranda to Deans, Administrative Officers, etc. from President Atkinson. 1937-1947 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous: Notices to faculty and staff from President Atkinson. 1937-1947 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous: Faculty meeting minutes. 1939-1943, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous: Faculty club. 1937-1947 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous: Campus Charity Drives. Red Cross and United Appeal. 1937-1947 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous: Advisory Council. 1937-1947 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous: Activities Schedule. 1941-1942 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous: Arizona Quarterly. 1944-1947 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Correspondence with other Institutions: General. 1937-1947 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Correspondence with other Institutions: General. 1937-1947 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Correspondence with other Institutions: Regarding Junior Colleges. 1939 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Correspondence with other Institutions: Regarding Governing Boards. 1939-1940 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Correspondence with other Institutions: Regarding Faculty renumeration from outside sources. 1940 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Correspondence with other Institutions: Wartime railroad transportation of Students. 1942-1944 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Correspondence with other Institutions: Selection of textbooks. 1941 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Correspondence with other Institutions: Regarding housing of women students. 1944 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Correspondence with other Institutions: Regarding way to attract gifts and donations. 1945 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Cecil Creel. Director of the Agricultural Extension, University of Nevada. 1937-1947 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Edward C. Elliott. President of Purdue University, Director of the American Council on Education. Includes correspondence with his Assistant F.C. Hockema. 1937-1947 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- F.D. Elliott. President of Kansas State College. 1937-1947 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Charles E. Friley. President of Iowa State College. 1937-1947 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- E.O. Holland. President of the State College of Washington. 1937-1947 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Rufus B. von KlienSmid. President/Chancellor of the University of Southern California. Includes correspondence regarding the Institute of World Affiars. 1937-1947 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- B.W. Montgomery. Superintendent of Phoenix Union High School and Junior College. 1937-1947 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- E.G. Paterson. President of Utah State Agricultural College. 1937-1947 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Robert G. Sproul. President of California, Berkeley. 1937-1947 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- A.L. Strand. President of Montana State College, Oregon State College. 1937-1947 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- J.F. Zimmerman. President of the University of New Mexico. 1937-1947 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- U.S. Congressmen: Henery Fountain Ashurst. Senate. 1937-1943 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- U.S. Congressmen: Carl Hayden. Senate. 1939-1947 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- U.S. Congressmen: Carl Hayden. Senate. 1939-1947 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- U.S. Congressmen: Carl Hayden. Senate. 1939-1947 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- U.S. Congressmen: Carl Hayden. Senate. 1939-1947 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- U.S. Congressmen: Carl Hayden. Senate. 1939-1947 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- U.S. Congressmen: Carl Hayden. Senate. 1939-1947 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- U.S. Congressmen: Carl Hayden. 1939-1947 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- U.S. Congressmen: Ernest W. McFarland. Senate. 1941-1947 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- U.S. Congressmen: Richard F. Harless. House of Representatives. 1942-1947 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- U.S. Congressmen: John R. Murdock. House of Representatives. 1937-1947 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- U.S. Congressmen: John R. Murdock. House of Representatives. 1937-1947 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- U.S. Congressmen: Various. 1937-1947 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous U.S. Offices and Departments: President Atkinson to President Franklin D. Roosevelt. 1939-1941 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous U.S. Offices and Departments: U.S Army Air Force. 1937-1947 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous U.S. Offices and Departments: Civil Service Commission. 1937-1947 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous U.S. Offices and Departments: U.S. Department of Agriculture. M.L. Wilson, Under Secretary and as Director of Extension. 1937-1940, 1940-1945 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous U.S. Offices and Departments: U.S Department of Agriculture. Conference on Man and Nature in the Great Plains Basin, Flagstaff, Arizona. September 4, 1939- September 6, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous U.S. Offices and Departments: U.S Department of Agriculture. Various and miscellaneous. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  Includes correspondence with Secretary of Agriculture Henry A. Wallace, the extension service, the Office of Experiment Stations, and the Soil Conservation Service.
- Miscellaneous U.S. Offices and Departments: U.S Department of the Interior. Repayment Commission. 1937-1938 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous U.S. Offices and Departments: U.S. Department of the Interior. National Park Service., 1937-1947 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous U.S. Offices and Departments: U.S. Navy. 1937-1947 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous U.S. Offices and Departments: U.S. Office of Education. Federal Sercurity Agency. 1937-1947 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous U.S. Offices and Departments: U.S. Office of Education. Federal Sercurity Agency. 1937-1947 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous U.S. Offices and Departments: U.S. Office of War Information. 1937-1947 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous U.S. Offices and Departments: U.S War Manpower Commission. 1937-1947 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous U.S. Offices and Departments: U.S Miscellaneous Departments. 1937-1947 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Arizona State Officials and Departments: Governors. R.C. Stanford. 1938 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Arizona State Officials and Departments: Governors. Robert T. Jones. 1938-1941 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Arizona State Officials and Departments: Governors. Sidney P. Osborn. 1940-1947 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Arizona State Officials and Departments: Governors. Sidney P. Osborn. 1940-1947 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Arizona State Officials and Departments: Governors. Sidney P. Osborn. 1940-1947 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Arizona State Officials and Departments: Arizona Attorney General. 1937-1947 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Arizona State Officials and Departments: Arizona Department of Public Instruction/Department of Education. 1937-1947 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Arizona State Officials and Departments: Arizona Department of Public Instruction/Department of Education. 1937-1947 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Arizona State Officials and Departments: Arizona State Board of Education. Meeting minutes. 1937-1941 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Arizona State Officials and Departments: Arizona State Fair Commission. 1937-1947 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Arizona State Officials and Departments: Arizona State Laboratory. Includes letters of Director Robert A. Greene while in military service. 1941 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Arizona State Officials and Departments: Arizona State Legislature. Senator Hubert H. D'Autremont. 1937-1947 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Arizona State Officials and Departments: Arizona State Legislature. Senator William F. Kimball. 1937-1947 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Arizona State Officials and Departments: Arizona State Legislature. House representative Robert H. Forbes. 1937-1947 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Arizona State Officials and Departments: Arizona State Legislature. Various. 1937-1947 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Arizona State Officials and Departments: Various Arizona State departments. Includes Department of Health, State Hospital, Industrial Commission, and Secretary of State. (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Board of Regents: General. 1937-1947 (Box 39a, Folder 1)
- Board of Regents: General. 1937-1947 (Box 39a, Folder 2)
- Board of Regents: General. 1937-1947 (Box 39a, Folder 3)
- Board of Regents: General. 1937-1947 (Box 39a, Folder 4)
- Board of Regents: M.O. Best. 1939-1947 (Box 39a, Folder 5)
- Board of Regents: M.O. Best. 1939-1947 (Box 39a, Folder 6)
- Board of Regents: A.M. Crawford. 1936-1946 (Box 39a, Folder 7)
- Board of Regents: A.M. Crawford. 1936-1946 (Box 39a, Folder 8)
- Board of Regents: E.E. Ellinwood. 1937-1940 (Box 39a, Folder 9)
- Board of Regents: E.E. Ellinwood. 1937-1940 (Box 39a, Folder 10)
  The later addition of addition Board of Regents files made it necessary to add the Box 39a.
- Board of Regents: Roland Ellsworth. 1943-1947 (Box 39b, Folder 1)
- Board of Regents: Martin Gentry. 1937-1943 (Box 39b, Folder 2)
- Board of Regents: Mrs. Joseph Madision Greer. 1941-1947 (Box 39b, Folder 3)
- Board of Regents: Clarence E. Houston. 1942-1947 (Box 39b, Folder 4)
- Board of Regents: Elbert T. Houston. 1937-1940 (Box 39b, Folder 5)
- Board of Regents: Cleaon T. Knapp. 1940-1947 (Box 39b, Folder 6)
- Board of Regents: H.S. McCluskey. 1937-1940 (Box 39b, Folder 7)
- Board of Regents: Jack B. Martin. 1937-1947 (Box 39b, Folder 8)
- Board of Regents: Halbert W. Miller. 1937-1940 (Box 39b, Folder 9)
- Board of Regents: Joseph H. Morgan. 1943-1945 (Box 39b, Folder 10)
- Board of Regents: Sam H. Morris. 1943-1947 (Box 39b, Folder 11)
- Board of Regents: Sam H. Morris. 1943-1947 (Box 39b, Folder 12)
- Board of Regents: John C. Scott. 1945-1947 (Box 39b, Folder 13)
- Board of Regents: William W. Stevenson. 1946-1947 (Box 39b, Folder 14)
- Board of Regents: William H. Westover. 1937-1945 (Box 39b, Folder 15)
  The latter acquisition of additional Board of Regente files made it necessary to add Box 39b.
- Arizona Colleges and Organizations: Arizona State Teachers College/Arizona State College, Flagstaff. Includes correspondence regarding President Atkinson's Commencement Address. May 26, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Arizona Colleges and Organizations: Arizona State Collge, Flagstaff. 1937-1947 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Arizona Colleges and Organizations: Arizona State Teachers College/Arizona State College, Tempe. 1937-1947 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Arizona Colleges and Organizations: Gila Junior College, Thatcher. Includes correspondence regarding President Atkinson's Commenecement Address. May 20, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Arizona Colleges and Organizations: Agricultural Co-ordinating Council. 1939-1940 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Arizona Colleges and Organizations: Arizona Cattle Growers' Association. Includes correspondence regarding various speeched made by President Atkinson. 1938-1942, 1945-1946 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Arizona Colleges and Organizations: Arizona Citrus Growers. Includes correspondence regarding President Atkinson's speech. 1941 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Arizona Colleges and Organizations: Arizona Education Association. Includes correspondence regarding President Atkinson's radio talk. April 30, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Arizona Colleges and Organizations: Arizona Farm Bureau Association. Includes correspondence regarding President Atkinson's speech. November 18, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Arizona Colleges and Organizations: Arizona Pioneers' Historical Society. Includes correspondence with Robert H. Forbes and Mrs. George F. Kitt. 1937-1947 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Arizona Colleges and Organizations: Arizona State Committee on Nutrition. 1940-1942 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Arizona Colleges and Organizations: Arizona Wool Growers' Association. Includes correspondence regarding President Atkinson's speeches in July 1938 and 1939. 1938-1939 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Arizona Colleges and Organizations: Tucson Chamber of Commerce. Includes correspondence regarding President Atkinson's address at the First Annual Aviation Conference, November 16, 1945. 1937-1947 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Arizona Colleges and Organizations: Tucson Sunshine Climate Club. 1937-1947 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Arizona Colleges and Organizations: Tucson Y.M.C.A. Includes correspondence regaring two speeched given by President Atkinson. 1938 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Arizona Colleges and Organizations: Westminster Foundation, Presbyterian Church, Tucson. Includes correspondence with Cleveland Dodge. 1937-1947 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- National Organizations: Association of Land-Grant Colleges & Universities: 75th Annual Meeting, Washington D.C. November 14-17, 1937. Includes correspondence regarding address by President Atkinson. 1937 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- National Organizations: Association of Land-Grant Colleges & Universities: 75th Annual Meeting, Washington D.C. November 14-17, 1937. Includes correspondence regarding address by President Atkinson. 1937 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- National Organizations: Association of Land-Grant Colleges & Universities: General Correspondence. 1937-1947 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- National Organizations: Association of Land-Grant Colleges & Universities: General Correspondence. 1937-1947 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- National Organizations: Association of Land-Grant Colleges & Universities: General Correspondence. 1937-1947 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- National Organizations: Association of Land-Grant Colleges & Universities: General Correspondence. 1937-1947 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- National Organizations: Association of Land-Grant Colleges & Universities: General Correspondence. 1937-1947 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- National Organizations: Association of Land-Grant Colleges & Universities: General Correspondence. 1937-1947 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- National Organizations: Association of Land-Grant Colleges & Universities: General Correspondence. 1937-1947 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- National Organizations: Association of Land-Grant Colleges & Universities: General Correspondence. 1937-1947 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- National Organizations: American Association of University Professors. 1937-1947 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- National Organizations: American Association of University Women. 1937-1947 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- National Organizations: American Council on Education. General Correspondence. 1937-1947 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- National Organizations: American Council on Education. Educational survey of UA, which includes preliminary correspondence with U.S. Office of Education. 1937 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- National Organizations: American Council on Education. Publication Higher Education and National Defense Various Issues. 1937-1947 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- National Organizations: Andean Anthropoligical Expedition, Inc. 1937-1947 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- National Organizations: Association of American Colleges. 1937-1947 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- National Organizations: Association of Governing Boards of State Universities and Allied Institutions. 1937-1947 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- National Organizations: Border Intercollegiate Athletic Conference. 1937-1947 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- National Organizations: Institute of International Education. 1937-1947 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- National Organizations: Institute of International Education. 1937-1947 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- National Organizations: National Association of State Universities. 1937-1947 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- National Organizations: National Association of State Universities. 1937-1947 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- National Organizations: National Association of State Universities. 1937-1947 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- National Organizations: National Collegiate Athletic Association. 1937-1947 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- National Organizations: National Committee for Cooperation in Character Building. 1937-1947 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- National Organizations: National Research Council. 1937-1947 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- National Organizations: North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools. 1937-1947 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- National Organizations: North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools. 1937-1947 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- National Organizations: North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools. Athletic Scholarships. 1937-1947 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- National Organizations: Phi Beta Kappa. 1937-1947 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Correspondence: General and miscellaneous. Includes letters to and from Mayor Fiorello LaGuardia, New York City, April 13 & 19, 1943. 1937-1947 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Correspondence: General and miscellaneous. Includes letters to and from Mayor Fiorello LaGuardia, New York City, April 13 & 19, 1943. 1937-1947 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Correspondence: General and miscellaneous. Includes letters to and from Mayor Fiorello LaGuardia, New York City, April 13 & 19, 1943. 1937-1947 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Correspondence: General and miscellaneous. Includes letters to and from Mayor Fiorello LaGuardia, New York City, April 13 & 19, 1943. 1937-1947 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Correspondence: General and miscellaneous. Includes letters to and from Mayor Fiorello LaGuardia, New York City, April 13 & 19, 1943. 1937-1947 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Correspondence: General and miscellaneous. Includes letters to and from Mayor Fiorello LaGuardia, New York City, April 13 & 19, 1943. 1937-1947 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Invitations: to participate, send representative, etc. 1937-1947 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Invitations: to support, endorse, etc. Includes correspondence with Margaret Sanger Slee regarding Planned Parenthood, 1946-1947. 1937-1947 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Invitations: Declined. To join, to serve on boards, committees, etc. 1937-1947 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Acknowledgements for various publications recieved. 1937-1947 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Acknowledgements for various publications recieved. 1937-1947 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Invitations: Accepted to speak/attend. 1937-1947 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Invitations: Accepted to speak/attend. 1937-1947 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Invitations: Accepted to speak/attend. 1937-1947 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Invitations: Accepted to speak/attend. 1937-1947 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Invitations: Accepted to speak/attend. 1937-1947 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Invitations: Accepted to speak/attend. 1937-1947 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Invitations: Accepted to speak/attend. 1937-1947 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Invitations: Declined to speak/attend. 1937-1947 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Invitations: Declined to speak/attend. 1937-1947 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Invitations: Declined to speak/attend. 1937-1947 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Requests: General University of Arizona information. 1937-1947 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  Includes President Atkinson's letter of January 3, 1940 to University of Wyoming President A.G. Crane describing athletic policies at UA.
- Requests: Information on UA appropriations, funding, fees. 1937-1947 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Requests: Information on UA buildings and their use; housing. 1937-1947 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Requests: Information on UA faculty. Salaries, tenure, retirement, etc. 1937-1947 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Requests: Information of UA students. Scholarship, enterance. 1937-1947 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Requests: Information on UA adjustment to war conditions. 1937-1947 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Requests: Information on UA post war plans, including veterans. 1937-1947 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Requests: Information on UA. Various topics including curriculum, former faculty and staff, faculty lecturers, and public relations functions. 1937-1947 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Requests: for names of persons to fill positions. 1937-1947 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Requests: for opinions. 1937-1947 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Requests: for publications. 1937-1947 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Requests: for meetings, miscellaneous information, and miscellaneous requests. 1937-1947 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous Thank You letters. 1937-1947 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Letters of recommendation. Includes various and miscellaneous correspondence written by President Atkinson. 1937-1947 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Personal Correspondence: Burridge D. Butler. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Personal Correspondence: Byron Cummings. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Personal Correspondence: Lewis W. Douglas. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Personal Correspondence: E.E. Ellinwood. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Personal Correspondence: Russell B. Fairgrieve. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Personal Correspondence: Columbus Giragi. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Personal Correspondence: Sophie Hart. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Personal Correspondence: Mrs. Dwight B. Heard. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Personal Correspondence: Herbert Hoover. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Personal Correspondence: Ada P. McCormick. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Personal Correspondence: William R. Mathews. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Personal Correspondence: E.P. Mathewson. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Personal Correspondence: Folsom Moore. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Personal Correspondence: Phelps Dodge Corporation. P.G. Beckett. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Personal Correspondence: Phelps Dodge Corporation. Louis S. Cates. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Personal Correspondence: Phelps Dodge Corporation. Cleveland Dodge and H.M Lavender; Law Library Gift. 1942 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Personal Correspondence: Clara (Fish) Roberts. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Personal Correspondence: Homer LeRoy Shantz. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Personal Correspondence: Arthur H. Wilde. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Personal Correspondence: Correspondence regarding guest editorials for the Phoenix Gazette. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Personal Correspondence: Correspondence regarding article for New York Times on Land-Grant Colleges, November 7, 1937. 1937 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Personal Correspondence: Various personal and professional memberships. 1937-1947 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Personal Correspondence: A.A. personal material and correspondence relating to Montana. 1928-1936 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Selection of President Atkinson's Successor: General Correspondence. 1946-1947 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Selection of President Atkinson's Successor: Candidates A - Z. 1946-1947 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Selection of President Atkinson's Successor: Candidates A - Z. 1946-1947 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Selection of President Atkinson's Successor: Candidates A - Z. 1946-1947 (Box 48, Folder 4)